A Guide to the Policy Office: General Assembly Legislation of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1990-1993.
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
General Assembly Legislation of the Policy Office of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder,
1990-1993.
The Library of Virginia
35539
Virginia. Govenor (1990-1994: Wilder).
24.85 cu. ft. (71 boxes)
Administrative Information
Arranged by General Assembly legislative session.
Access Restrictions
Office of the Attorney General legislative recommendations are protected by attorney-client privilege and are restricted from public access for 75 years per Code of Virginia 42.1-78, but have not been removed from the collection. These records are open for research but it will be necessary for an archivist to review certain files before they can be used by patrons for research purposes or before any copies of the records can be made. If you are planning to use these records, please contact Archives Reference Services for additional details before planning your research trip.
Acquisition Information
Accession 35539 was transferred by the Office of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, October 31, 1996.
Historical Information
Lawrence Douglas Wilder was born in Richmond, Va., on January 17, 1931. He graduated from Virginia Union University in 1951 and afterwards was drafted into the Army, where he served in the Korean War from 1952-1953 and received a bronze star. He then attended the Howard University School of Law and graduated in 1959. Douglas Wilder was elected to the Virginia Senate in 1969 as the first African American member since Reconstruction and served in the Senate for five terms. In 1985, he was elected to the office of Lieutenant Governor as the first African American to be elected to statewide office in Virginia. L. Douglas Wilder won the election for Governor of Virginia in 1989 and served from January 13, 1990 to January 14, 1994. He was the first African American to be elected as Governor in United States.
During the Wilder Administration, the Policy Office was headed by Walter McFarlane, Executive Assistant for Policy, and four Special Assistants: Richard Taylor (Health and Human Resources, and Education), Robert Blue (Finance and Natural Resources), Jeff Nuechterlein (Economic Development and Transportation), and Lynne Porfiri (Administration and Public Safety). The Policy Office was responsible for review and coordination of all policy matters, including: review of proposed legislation from agencies and Cabinet; formulation of the Governor's legislative initiatives; tracking legislation and serving as legislative liaison; review of General Assembly approved legislation submitted to the Governor for signature, amendment or veto; review of death penalty clemency requests, as well as other pardon and restoration of rights requests; review of legal settlements and other legal matters from the Office of the Attorney General's Office; review of proposed regulations; review of all matters pertaining to the judiciary and writs of habeas corpus; review of proposed executive orders; assistance with speech writing; serving as staff for Governor's special commissions; administrative support for Governor's Fellows program; serving as special interest liaison; acting as in-house counsel; and all correspondence with policy implications or pertaining to sensitive or controversial issues requiring legal overview.
Scope and Content
General Assembly Legislation, 1990-1993, is housed in 71 boxes and is arranged chronologically by year of legislative session, and by chamber and bill number thereunder. This series documents the Governor's Policy Office review of legislation approved by the General Assembly during the Wilder administration and provides policy positions and decisions of the administration. Legislative files usually contain the text of each bill; bill tracking information; Governor's Summaries (prepared by the Division of Legislative Services; Legislative Action Summaries (prepared by the Dept. of Planning and Budget); Bill Reviews/Recommendations to the Governor (prepared by Cabinet Secretary and agency); Policy Office Summary sheet; and Attorney General Recommendations to the Governor (restricted 75 years - attorney-client privilege). Files may also include correspondence, reports and other background documentation. Include House of Delegates Bills, Senate Bills, Amended/Reenrolled legislation, Legislation by date of approval, Vetoed legislation, and Special Session legislation.
Each Governor's Summary prepared by the Division of Legislative Services contains the bill number, patron, bill summary, conflicts, comments and name of the reviewer. Bill Reviews/Recommendations are prepared by the agency most affected by the legislation and include a summary of the bill, fiscal and policy impact, and agency and secretary recommendations and signatures. Legislative Impact Statements prepared by the Dept. of Planning and Budget include patron, bill number, title, summary/purpose of the bill, fiscal impact estimates, expenditure and paperwork impact, fiscal (operating and capital) implications, program and policy implications; description of specific agency/subdivision affected by the legislation and comments. Policy Office summary sheets include general information, constituent comments, policy office analysis and recommendations as to whether to sign, amend or veto. The Office of the Attorney General's Recommendations to the Governor contain check boxes noting if the legislation conflicts with existing laws or the Virginia and Federal constitutions, as well as any suggested amendments or comments. The Attorney General's Recommendations are restricted due to attorney-client privilege.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. General Assembly Legislation, 1990-1994.
Contents List
- General Assembly Legislation, 1990.
  - House of Delegates Bills, 1990.
    - HB 1 (90) Withdrawal of appeals to Circuit Court, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - HB 2 (90) Exemption from property tax - Frederick United Methodist Housing Development Corp., 1990. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - HB 3 (90) Charter for the City of Hampton, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - HB 4 (90) Expenses for members of the Board of Forestry, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - HB 5 (90) Powers of teh State Air Pollution Control Board, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - HB 6 (90) Affidavits required in civil actions, damages for motor vehicles, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - HB 8 (90) Exemption from property tax (Wise School of Dance, Inc.), 1990. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - HB 10 (90) Special license plates and fees, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - HB 11 (90) Conservators of the Peace, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - HB 16 (90) Guest State Scenic River, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - HB 17 (90) Admissability into evidence - copies of medical records, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - HB 18 (90) - Presentation of evidence of medical reports, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - HB 19 (90) Statute of limitations for misdemeanors, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - HB 21 (90) Exemption for property tax - Virginia Beach Ecumenical Housing, Inc., 1990. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - HB 25 (90) Charter for the City of Bristol, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - HB 26 (90) Exemption from property tax - Bellvue, Inc., 1990. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - HB 27 (90) Exemption from property tax - Memorial Properties, Inc., 1990. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - HB 29 (90) Appropriating public revenues, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - HB 34 (90) Charter for the City of Charlottesville (Redevelopment and Housing Authority), 1990. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - HB 35 (90) Federal financial institutions reform legislation, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - HB 36 (90) Exemption from property tax - Brethren Housing Corp., 1990. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - HB 37 (90) Eligibility for real estate exemption or deferral, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - HB 38 (90) Charter for the City of Manassas, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - HB 39 (90) Charter for the City of Manassas, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - HB 40 (90) Exemption from property tax - Westover Hills Community Center, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - HB 41 (90) Motor boat registration, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - HB 42 (90) Special lien for demolishing unsafe and unsanitary buildings, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - HB 44 (90) Exemption from property tax - Mountain Empire Older Citizens, Inc., 1990. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - HB 45 (90) Exemption from property tax - Alternative House, Inc., 1990. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - HB 46 (90) Relief for King and Queen County, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - HB 47 (90) Licensing requirement of mortgage lenders and brokers, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - HB 48 (90) Distribution procedures and effectiv sunset dates for distribution of state recordation taxes to cities and counties, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - HB 50 (90) Insurance consultants, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - HB 51 (90) Retail sales and use tax exemptions, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - HB 52 (90) Abandoned motor vehicles, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - HB 53 (90) Charter for the Town of Vinton, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - HB 55 (90) Exemption from property tax - Patrick Henry Boys Plantation, Inc., 1990. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - HB 56 (90) Riverside Regional Jail Authority, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - HB 57 (90) Charter for the City of Richmond, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - HB 58 (90) Registration under the Securities Act, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - HB 60 (90) Exemption from securities registration for certain foreign issuers, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - HB 62 (90) Annual fees paid by mortgage lenders and brokers, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - HB 63 (90) Lenders making real estate loans, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - HB 64 (90) Licenses and places of business of mortgage lenders and brokers, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - HB 65 (90) Exemption from property tax - Richmond Discoveries, Inc., 1990. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - HB 68 (90) ABC laws and mixed beverage licenses, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - HB 70 (90) ABC lawas and grounds for license refusal, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - HB 74 (90) Assessment of court costs for courthouse construction, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - HB 76 (90) Exemption from property tax - Community Memorial Hospital, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - HB 77 (90) Exemption from property tax - MARC of Virginia, Inc., 1990. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - HB 78 (90) Sewage disposal and inspection of alternate discharge sewage systems, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - HB 80 (90) Exemption from property tax - Jewish Family Services, Inc., 1990. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - HB 82 (90) Charter for the City of Roanoke, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - HB 83 (90) Retail sales and use tax exemptions, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - HB 84 (90) Definition of tractor truck, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - HB 85 (90) Credit for payment of the motor fuels tax by motor carriers, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - HB 86 (90) Free use of toll facilities, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - HB 87 (90) Motor fuel carriers, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - HB 88 (90) Exemption from property tax - Historic Farmville, Inc., 1990. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - HB 92 (90) Exemption from property tax - Stafford United Methodis Housing Development Corp., 1990. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - HB 93 (90) Charter for the Town of Hillsboro (Loudoun Co.), 1990. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - HB 94 (90) Exemption from property tax - Burwell-Van Lennep Foundation, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - HB 95 (90) Exemption from property tax - Waterman's Museum, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - HB 96 (90) Expenses incurred for the care and provision of seized animals, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - HB 97 (90) Local government authority to require water testing, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - HB 98 (90) County construction and improvement of primary and secondary highways, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - HB 99 (90) Powers and duties of political subdivisions, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - HB 101 (90) Exemption from property tax - Richmond Lodge No. 45 of the Benevolent and Protective Order of the Elks, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - HB 102 (90) Exemption from property tax - City Light Development Corp., 1990. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - HB 103( 90) Procurement of design-build construction contracts, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - HB 105 (90) Expedited land development review procedure in the urban county executive form of government, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - HB 106 (90) Charter for the Town of Rich Creek (Giles Co.), 1990. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - HB 109 (90) Charter for the Town of Lebanon, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - HB 112 (90) Regulation of child care services and facilities by counties, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - HB 114 (90) Assessing owners of abutting property for improvements by counties, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - HB 115 (90) Restriction of activities of former officers and employees in counties, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - HB 118 (90) Motor vehicle carriers, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - HB 119 (90) Regulatory revenue taxes and application for review and correction by the SCC, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - HB 120 (90) Retail sales and use tax exemption, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - HB 123 (90) Exemption from property tax - Richmond Virginia Seminary, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - HB 124 (90) Charter for the Town of Bowling Green (Caroline Co.), 1990. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - HB 125 (90) Exemption from property tax - Drug Action Center, Inc., 1990. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - HB 127 (90) Exemption from property tax - Richmond Residential Services, Inc., 1990. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - HB 128 (90) Exemption from property tax - Military Retirees Club of Richmond Virginia, Inc., 1990. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - HB 129 (90) Charter for the County of Chesterfield, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - HB 132 (90) Exemption from property tax - Parent-Child Development Center, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - HB 134 (90) Form of a deed, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - HB 138 (90) Uniform Commercial Code, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - HB 140 (90) Sale of money orders, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - HB 141 (90) Non-profit debt counseling agencies, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - HB 142 (90) Special examinators of savings institutions, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - HB 143 (90) Charges of loan by consumer finance companies, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - HB 148 (90) County taxes on the sale of food and beverages, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - HB 149 (90) Division of Risk Management, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - HB 150 (90) Legislative information officers, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - HB 156 (90) Motor vehicle safety inspections, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - HB 157 (90) Local government authority to require analysis of water, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - HB 158 (90) Disposal of unclaimed firearms, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - HB 159 (90) Income tax returns filed by corporations, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - HB 161 (90) Involuntary detention of mentally ill persons, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - HB 163 (90) Parking facility bonds, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - HB 167 (90) Transacting business without a certificate of authorization, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - HB 168 (90) Packaging of game, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - HB 169 (90) Motor vehicle sales and use exemptions, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - HB 173 (90) Methods of serving process, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - HB 175 (90) Civil actions, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - HB 176 (90) Injury to church or cemetery property, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - HB 177 (90) Motor vehicle dealers, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - HB 179 (90) Asbestos inspections, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - HB 181 (90) Supreme Court reports, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - HB 184 (90) Disclaimer to succession of property, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - HB 185 (90) Division of trusts, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - HB 187 (90) Fiduciary security transfers, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - HB 191 (90) Photocopy fees - Commissioners of Revenue, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - HB 192 (90) Aboveground storage tanks, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - HB 193 (90) Refunds - small water charges and sewer utility charges, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - HB 194 (90) SCC service of process, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - HB 195 (90) Daycare programs, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - HB 196 (90) Water protection permit, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - HB 198 (90) Motor vehicle dealers, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - HB 199 (90) Motor vehicle dealers - advertising, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - HB 201 (90) State Lottery Board, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - HB 205 (90) Merchants' capital tax, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - HB 206 (90) Voluntary annexation, transition and immunity settlements among local governments, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - HB 207 (90) Uniform Commerical Code, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - HB 209 (90) County regulation of parking on secondary highways, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - HB 210 (90) Dept. of Social Services representation, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - HB 213 (90) Public Defender Commission, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - HB 214 (90) Public defender duties, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - HB 215 (90) State debt, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - HB 216 (90) Local debt, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - HB 218 (90) Beneficiary payments under line of duty, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - HB 219 (90) Local motor vehicle licenses, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - HB 220 (90) Local government service districts, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - HB 221 (90) Virginia Aviation Museum, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - HB 223 (90) Unregistered firearm mufflers or silencers, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - HB 224 (90) Chain of custody, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - HB 226 (09) Certificates of analysis, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - HB 228 (09) Motor vehicle registration cards, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - HB 229 (09) Motor vehicle laws, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - HB 231 (09) Judicial conference of Virginia, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - HB 233 (09) Distribution of drugs, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - HB 236 (09) Adoption services, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - HB 237 (09) Deeds of trust, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - HB 238 (09) Money in control of the court, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - HB 239 (09) Clerk's fees, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - HB 240 (90) Home/electronic incarceration, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - HB 245 (90) Candidate qualifications, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - HB 246 (90) Itemized statements for patients, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - HB 248 (90) Removal of unsafe vehicles from service, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - HB 251 (90) Virginia Code Commission, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - HB 252 (90) Virginia Voluntary Formulary, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - HB 256 (90) School Board member salaries, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - HB 257 (90) Uniform Custodial Trust Act, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - HB 259 (90) Virginia Recreational Facilities Authority, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - HB 261 (90) Virginia Health Planning Board, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - HB 262 (90) Licensed practical nurse teaching authority, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - HB 264 (90) Daycare programs, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - HB 266 (90) Dorothy S. McDiarmid, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - HB 267 (90) Grants to libraries, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - HB 270 (90) Donations of food, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - HB 277 (90) Contracts for asbestos projects, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - HB 279 (90) Income tax credits for agricultural equipment, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - HB 280 (90) Insurance - Unfair trade practices, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - HB 281 (90) Elderly and disabled persons - Real estate tax exemptions, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - HB 282 (90) Supreme Court and Court of Appeals reports, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - HB 284 (90) Storage of motor vehicles, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - HB 287 (90) Prohibition on setting fishing nets in marked channels, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - HB 292 (90) Profits from crime, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - HB 294 (90) Crime victim awards, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - HB 296 (90) Industrial Commission, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - HB 297 (90) Criminal Injuries Compensation Fund, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - HB 298 (90) Criminial Injuries Compensation Fund, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - HB 299 (90) Police lines, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - HB 301 (90) Virginia Public Procurement Act, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - HB 303 (90) Workers Compensation Act, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - HB 304 (90) Employing blind persons, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - HB 305 (90) Liability Insurance - Competition hearing and reports, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - HB 307 (90) Dinwiddie Airport and Industrial Authority, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - HB 308 (90) Regulation of asbestos contractors and laborers, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - HB 309 (90) Inspection standards for identifying asbestos, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - HB 310 (90) Certificates of satisfaction, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - HB 311 (90) Secretary of the Commonwealth - Service of process, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - HB 312 (90) Suspension or tolling of statute of limitations, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - HB 313 (90) Intake of juveniles, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - HB 316 (90) Immediate custody of children, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - HB 318 (90) Carrying weapons on school property, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - HB 320 (90) Division of Forensic Science, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - HB 326 (90) Christopher Newport College Board of Visitors, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - HB 327 (90) Christopher Newport College - Master's degree programs, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - HB 328 (90) Hospital utilization review, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - HB 329 (90) State and local government conflict of interest acts, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - HB 330 (90) Motor vehicle dealers, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - HB 331 (90) Vehicle service facilities, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - HB 332 (90) Parole, probation and work release, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - HB 333 (90) Sale of property - Judgments, taxes and levies, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - HB 334 (90) Stock Corporation Act, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - HB 338 (90) Virginia Birth-Related Neurological Injury Compensation Act, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - HB 339 (90) Motor vehicles, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - HB 340 (90) Prisoners - Employment, education, rehabilitation programs, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - HB 343 (90) Local government - Liability in operation of recreational facilities, parks and playgrounds, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - HB 347 (90) Air pollution permits, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - HB 348 (90) Local motor vehicle licenses, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - HB 349 (90) State aid and length of school year, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - HB 353 (90) Personal property tax - Prorated funds, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - HB 354 (90) Visually handicapped, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - HB 355 (90) State grievance procedure, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - HB 357 (90) Capital murder, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - HB 358 (90) Literary Fund, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - HB 362 (90) Forfeiture of weapons used in commission of a crime, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - HB 363 (90) Bingo and raffles, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - HB 367 (90) Write-in votes and voting equipment, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - HB 368 (90) Regional emergence medical services councils, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - HB 371 (90) Public utilities and public service companies, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - HB 372 (90) Health services, legal service, dental and optometric plans, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - HB 373 (90) Workers' compensation claims, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - HB 374 (90) Real estate tax exemptions - Elderly and disabled, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - HB 375 (90) Institutions of higher education - Leases, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 2)